{
    "questions":[{
        "question": "Which number is the Odd one out :- 84129,32418, 36119, 19614, 12512",
        "choice1": "84129",
        "choice2": "32418",
        "choice3": "12512",
        "choice4": "19614",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "Evaluate the expression 1 + 1 in base 2 ",
        "choice1": "10",
        "choice2": "11",
        "choice3": "Two (2)",
        "choice4": "01",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Greek letter/symbol used to symbolize summation in Mathematics",
        "choice1": "Delta",
        "choice2": "Omega",
        "choice3": "Sigma",
        "choice4": "Alpha",
        "answer": 3
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "To the nearest whole number, how many radians are in a whole circle ?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "3",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 2
    }
    ,{
        "question": "If 5 boys take 7 hours to pack 35 cartoons, then how many boys can pack 65 cartoons in 3 hours?",
        "choice1": "65",
        "choice2": "12",
        "choice3": "56",
        "choice4": "None of the Above",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The average of first 50 natural numbers is ----------------------------- ?",
        "choice1": "25.0",
        "choice2": "25.5",
        "choice3": "30.5",
        "choice4": "26.0",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fill in the blank in this sequence :- 4, 6, 12, 14, 28, 30, (-----) ?",
        "choice1": "35",
        "choice2": "60",
        "choice3": "36",
        "choice4": "72",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "If each edge of a cube is increased by 50%, what is the corresponding increase in the surface area ?",
        "choice1": "125%",
        "choice2": "200%",
        "choice3": "150%",
        "choice4": "22.5%",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The diagonals of a rhombus are 30cm and 40cm long, find the length of the side ?",
        "choice1": "35cm",
        "choice2": "30cm",
        "choice3": "None of the Above",
        "choice4": "25cm",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "All natural numbers and 0 are called the ------------------ numbers.",
        "choice1": "Whole",
        "choice2": "Rational",
        "choice3": "Real",
        "choice4": "Integer",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The wages of 10 workers for a six-day week is $ 1200. What are the one dayâ€™s wages of 4 workers?",
        "choice1": "$40",
        "choice2": "$32",
        "choice3": "$80",
        "choice4": "$24",
        "answer": 3
    }

]
}